# Christina Stanczyk

Cherry Hill, NJ | 856-843-1202 | cstanczyk123@gmail.com

### **About Me**

I am a 24 year-old passionate student, currently enrolled in UPENN's PLS Coding Boot Camp. My hobbies include: reading, painting, singing and programming. I learn very quickly in fast-paced environments, since coming from the service industry. I am self-funding my education and desire a reliable work environment to gain more experience in the professional world.

#### Education

CERTIFICATE | EXPECTED GRADUATION MARCH 2022 | UNIVERSITY OF PENNSYLVANIA PLS CODING BOOT CAMP

August 2015 - 2018 | University of Colorado Boulder

Completed 82 credits towards a Bachelor of Science in Technology, Arts & Media Engineering.

HIGH SCHOOL DIPLOMA | MAY 2015 | CHERRY HILL HIGH SCHOOL EAST

#### **Skills & Abilities**

- Terminal
- Git Bash
- GitHub
- HTML5
- CSS3

- Flexbox
- C++
- Python
- Front-End Web Development
- JavaScript

## **Experience**

Manager & Bartender | el rey - Starr Restaurants | June 2021 to September 2021

I was promoted to be a Floor Manager at El Rey which made me responsible for supervising shifts from open to close. I was also in charge of sharing and reporting the analytics for each day.

SERVER & BARTENDER | JILL'S - St. JULIEN HOTEL & SPA | DECEMBER 2019 TO OCTOBER 2020

SERVER & BARTENDER | EL REY - STARR RESTAURANTS | MARCH 2018 TO OCTOBER 2019

Fundraiser & Telemarketer | Ruffalo Noel Levitz | January 2016 to july 2016

While attending CU Boulder, I worked at a call-center on campus on weeknights and weekends. I was responsible for calling alumni for the duration of my shift. I learned how to build rapport with donors over the phone and persuade them to assist funding for academic scholarships.